(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
ここはねぽらぼ学園！
This is NePoLaBo Academy!
部活もクラスも違うけど、ねねたち同じ学生寮に住んでるんだ！
Our clubs and classes are different, but we all live in the same dorm!
ふざけて、笑って、時々ケンカして。
Goofing off, laughing, and sometimes fighting.
でも集まると、なんか落ち着く！
But when we get together, it's somehow so relaxing!
今日も談話室賑やか。
The common room is lively again today.
誰かの声が聞こえるだけで、安心するんだよね。
Just hearing someone's voice makes me feel at ease.
この場所で、私たちだけの学寮祭を作るなんて、
Creating a dormitory festival just for us in this place...
楽しそうでワクワクする。
sounds fun and gets me excited.
さあ！
Now!
私たちの！
Our!
輝く青春が！
Our sparkling youth...
始まる！
begins!
ねぽらぼ学園 5周年記念！輝く学寮祭！
NePoLaBo Academy 5th Anniversary! Sparkling Dormitory Festival!
今日は学寮祭。生徒会が中心になって開催する、夏の一大イベント！
Today is the Dormitory Festival. A major summer event organized mainly by the student council!
会長からの頼みで、急遽ねぽらぼで出し物を考えることになったんだけど──
At the president's request, we had to suddenly come up with a performance for NePoLaBo...
何も考えられてな──い！！！！
But we haven't thought of anything at all!!!!
やばいよ...気づいたら、もう当日だよ〜〜〜！
This is bad... before I knew it, it's already the day of the event~~!
だから言ったじゃん！もっと早く集まって決めようって。
That's why I said it! Let's gather earlier and decide.
いや〜なんとかなるって思ってたんだけどな〜（笑）
Well~ I thought it would work out somehow~ (laughs)
うぅ...これはまずい...。
Ugh... this is bad...
変なことやったら、会長になんて言われるか......
If we do something weird, what will the student council president say...
よし、断ろう！！
Alright, let's turn it down!!
やめなー！当日に断れるわけないでしょ！
Stop it! There's no way you can turn it down on the day of!!
大丈夫大丈夫、ラミィちゃんならきっと許してくれるって♪
It's okay, it's okay, I'm sure Lamy-chan will forgive us♪
大丈夫大丈夫、ラミィちゃんならちょっとだけ許してくれるって♪
It's okay, it's okay, I'm sure Lamy-chan will forgive us just a little bit.
なんでラミィだけお嫁さん前提なのよっ！
Why is it assumed that only Lamy is getting married?!
……いや、まだ終わってない！学寮祭はお昼から……
...No, it's not over yet! The Academy Festival starts in the afternoon...
ほんのちょっとだけ、まだ時間はある！
There's still just a little bit of time left!
よし、とりあえず案を出してみよっか
Alright, let's try coming up with some ideas for now.
学校の祭りといえば……
Speaking of school festivals...
焼きそば、じゃがバター、唐揚げ、クレープ、ポテト……
yakisoba, buttered potatoes, fried chicken, crepes, fries...
食べ物しかないじゃん！！
It's all food!!
でも今から仕込みはちょっと無理かもね
But prepping ingredients might be a bit much from now on.
まあできるとしたら、炎天下でカラカラな喉に染み渡る……
Well, if there's one thing we can do...
ラミィ水！！
Lamy Water!! To quench that parched throat under the blazing sun!!
これは売れるぞ〜
This'll sell like crazy!
やめろぉぉぉ！！！
Stop it!!!
うっひょおぉ！しぼり出して〜
Whoo! Squeeze it out!
バカなこと言ってないで！もっと真面目に考えなさいって！
Stop talking nonsense! I told you to think about this more seriously!
そんなに言うならラミィちゃんは何がいいの？
If you say so, then what do you want to do, Lamy-chan?
ラミィ？そうだなあ……やっぱり歌は歌いたいし、
Me? Let me see... I definitely want to sing,
バンドとか、かな？
Maybe something like a band?
ふつう
Typical.
ひねりがない〜
No originality.
……フツー
...Ordinary.
こいつら……！
You guys...!
でもまあ、歌はいいかもね〜
But well, singing might be good.
ショート動画用にいろいろな曲練習してるし、その中から何かやってみる？
We've been practicing various songs for short videos, want to try one of those?
あ、じゃあね、あれやりたい！！元気いっぱいの、ねねたちにピッタリなやつ！！
Oh, then I want to do THAT one!! The energetic one that's perfect for us!!
あ〜〜, あれね！
Ah~~, that one!
いいんじゃない！
Sounds good!
じゃ, とりあえずやってみますか！
Then, shall we give it a try for now?
キメマスター！！
Kime Master!!
前人未到の未踏地だよなあ
It's a so-called unexplored territory where no one has gone before, right?
そいりゃー！
Soiya!
キメマスター！！
作詞・作曲：Q-MHz
Kime Master!!
Lyrics & Composition: Q-MHz
生まれかわる一歩目は
The first step to being reborn...
一歩目が大事さ恐れない
The first step is important, don't be afraid
何度でも平気な顔で走り出して
Running out with a straight face over and over again
行かなきゃ！上々の気分さ
I've gotta go! I'm in the best mood
やってみたいことには欲張りだね
I'm greedy for the things I want to try
欲張りごめんね直さないよ
Sorry for being greedy, I won't change
何度でも未来を書き換えたくなるのさ
I feel like rewriting the future over and over
行かなきゃ！最高の仲間と
I've gotta go! With the best companions
星になろうよ輝きたいよ
Let's become stars, I want to shine
今は今だけ
Right now, just for now
後悔しないようにねっ
Don't let there be any regrets!
さあおいで MONSTERS
Come on, MONSTERS
暴れば MONSTERS
Run wild, MONSTERS
こんなにも無敵 PIKA STARS!
So invincible, PIKA STARS!
夢が KIRA-KIRA
Dreams are KIRA-KIRA
無駄に KIRA-KIRA？
Uselessly KIRA-KIRA?
前進だ DOKA-DOKA!
Move forward, DOKA-DOKA!
はわっ 通りまる
Hawa! Passing through
キマッちゃってる！
We're on a roll!
全速モードでよいしょっしょ
In full speed mode, let's go, let's go
制限はね無視だよ
Ignore the limits, you know
なんでもかんでもやっぱっぱ
Anything and everything, you know
全力がいいよね
Full power is the best, right?
笑顔あり
With smiles,
キメ顔あり
with cool poses
最強BIG BANG 狙っちゃえ未来！
Strongest BIG BANG, aim for the future!
チェストー！
CHESTO!
手と取りあったらるんたった
If we take each other's hands, run-ta-ta
怖くはないよね
It's not scary, is it?
夢の計測メーターは振り切れそうだよ
The dream measurement meter is about to max out
地球からやってきたボクらは
We who came from Earth
本日も Go ahead! Go ahead!
Today too, Go ahead! Go ahead!
怒られるまで？
Until we get scolded?
怒られても止まらないのです
Even if we get scolded, we won't stop
騒がしくてもごめんなさーい！
Sorry for being noisy!
先陣誰だい？ボクらだい！
Who's at the vanguard? It's us!
いわゆる前人未到の未踏地だよなあ
It's a so-called unexplored territory where no one has gone before, right?
そいりゃー！
Soiya!
譲らないないないな百歩目も
The hundredth step I won't give up, up, up
百歩譲るなんて負けよダメ日よ
To give in a hundred steps is a loss, it's a bad day
ゴールへのロードは砂利と岩だらけで
The road to the goal is full of gravel and rocks
泣いても顔は “にっかり”
Even if I cry, my face is "grinning"
そんな時あきらめ悪く進め
At times like that, keep going with persistence
だってほらあきらめたくない夢が
Because, you see, the dream I don't want to give up
進化してみんなを果ての果ての空へ
has evolved, taking everyone to the furthest, furthest sky
連れ去るボクら地上の子
We, the children of the earth, will take you away
憧れたんだ
I yearned for it
星の光は消えないときめき
The starlight is an undying throb
心拍数上がりまくり
Heart rate rising like crazy
さあ踊んで MONSTERS
Come on, dance, MONSTERS
溢れちゃお MONSTERS
Let it overflow, MONSTERS
大胆で不敵 PIKA STARS!
Daring and fearless, PIKA STARS!
鼓動ときめきが上昇中
Throb and excitement are rising
つまり絶好調中
In other words, in peak condition
あ、サビきます
Ah, the chorus is coming
たぶん勝利は
Probably the victory is...
キマッちゃってる！
Decided!
いいトコだったのに！
It was just getting to the good part!
バンドじゃないからせっせっせ
Since we're not a band, se-se-se
カッコつけなければ
If we don't act cool
バンドじゃないからよいよいよい
Since we're not a band, yoi-yoi-yoi
カッコがつくのだよ
It'll look cool
バカ騒ぎ やんちゃ騒ぎ
Fooling around, mischievous behavior
やったもん勝ち狙っちゃえ未来！
Winner takes all, aim for the future!
チェストー！
CHESTO!
銀河のどっかの頂点に旗を立てるまで
Until we plant our flag on some peak in the galaxy
ニューレコードの更新は続くんだってば
The updating of new records will continue, I'm telling you
地球からやってきたボクらよ
We who came from Earth
やりまくれ Go ahead! Go ahead!
Do it all, Go ahead! Go ahead!
さあ次の星へ！
Now, to the next star!
一歩が百歩の始まり
One step is the beginning of a hundred
だから行こうよすぐに行こうよ
So let's go, let's go right now
無理は道理よりも強引だなー
Pushing too hard is more forceful than reason
瞬間をキミと一緒にね
That moment, together with you
MONSTER!
真っ暗な空かもしれないけどボクらは負けない
It might be a pitch-black sky, but we won't lose
お目々を開いてお目々を離すなよー
Open your eyes, don't look away!
MONSTER! HEY! MONSTER! HEY! MONSTER!
前人未到の宇宙に全速の全力で Goだ Yeah!!
Into the unexplored universe, at full speed and full power, let's go, Yeah!!
全開かい そうだそうだっ
Are you at full throttle? Yes, that's right!
地球はブルーだブルーだっ
The Earth is blue, so blue!
ぜんぶを欲しがれ EARTH女子!
Want it all, Earth Girls!
全開かい そうかもそうかもっ
Are you at full throttle? Maybe, just maybe!
宇宙のスターにスターにっ
To be a star, a star in the universe!
なりたい! なりたい!
I want to be! I want to be!
なれそう? なれそうだよう!
Can I be? It looks like I can!
キマっちゃったしね!
We've decided on it!
全速モードでよいしょっしょ 制限はね 無視だよ
Yoishossho at full speed mode, limitations are ignored!
なんでもかんでもやっぱっぱ 全力がいいよね
Whatever it is, doing our best is the best!
メガ回れ ヒメガ回れ
Spin around mega, spin around hime-mega
最強 BIG BANG 狙っちゃえ未来!
Aim for the future with the strongest BIG BANG!
チェストー!
Chest!
手とりあったるんたった 怖くはないよね
Holding hands, run-tatta, it's not scary, is it?
夢の計測メーターは 振り切れそうだよ
The dream measurement meter is about to fly off!
地球から やってきたボクラは
We, who came from Earth,
本日も Go ahead! Go ahead!
Are still going ahead today! Go ahead!
怒られるまで…
Until we get scolded...
…怒られても止まらないのです
...even if we get scolded, we won't stop!
最後の最後もごめんなさーい!
So sorry, even at the very end!
先鋒だれだい? ボクらだい!
Who's the vanguard? We are!
いわゆる前人未踏の未踏地だよなあ
It's an unprecedented, uncharted territory!
もう一回っ!
One more time!
大いなる一歩さ ボクらと最高速で
A great step forward at top speed with us!
前人未踏の未踏地へ Go!!
To the unprecedented, uncharted territory, Go!!
そいやー!
Soiya!
桃鈴ねね: よーっし、次はバンドだ!
Momosuzu Nene: Alright, next is the band!
桃鈴ねね: できる曲を片っ端からやっていこう〜!!
Momosuzu Nene: Let's do every song we can!
獅白ぼたん: でもあたしたち、楽器できなくない……?
Shishiro Botan: But we can't play instruments, can we...?
尾丸ポルカ: こういうのはね、雰囲気っていうやつ、雰囲気が大事だから!
Omaru Polka: These things are all about the vibe! The vibe is what's important!
尾丸ポルカ: 頑張っている姿を見せれば、それでOK!
Omaru Polka: If we show them we're doing our best, it'll be fine!
雪花ラミィ: バカにしといて結局やるのね…
Yukihana Lamy: You say it's stupid, but you're doing it in the end...
桃鈴ねね: じゃあまず、誰が何をやるのか決めよう〜!
Momosuzu Nene: Then first, let's decide who's doing what!
桃鈴ねね: ねねはギターっ!!
Momosuzu Nene: Nene is on guitar!
獅白ぼたん: じゃあ、ししろんはドラムかな〜
Shishiro Botan: Then Shishiron will do drums, I guess.
尾丸ポルカ: ポルカはベースで〜!
Omaru Polka: Polka is on bass!
雪花ラミィ: じゃあラミィは、シンセ…やろうかなっ
Yukihana Lamy: Then Lamy will do... the synth, maybe.
尾丸ポルカ: そうしたら演出も考えないとな〜
Omaru Polka: In that case, we need to think about the stage production too.
桃鈴ねね: 派手にドッカーンってしたい!!
Momosuzu Nene: I want to go out with a flashy boom!
雪花ラミィ: ざっくりだな〜
Yukihana Lamy: That's pretty vague.
獅白ぼたん: サビにキャノンとか出す?
Shishiro Botan: Should we fire cannons during the chorus?
桃鈴ねね: いいね!
Momosuzu Nene: Sounds good!
桃鈴ねね: 照明もレーザー出したりとかで、ピカピカにしていこう!
Momosuzu Nene: Let's have the lights firing lasers and make it all sparkly!
尾丸ポルカ: じゃあ、ねねはポルカと動き回ってパフォーマンスしよう!
Omaru Polka: Then Nene and Polka will move around and perform!
桃鈴ねね: やるやる、任せて〜!!
Momosuzu Nene: I'll do it, leave it to me!
雪花ラミィ: だ、大丈夫か?
Yukihana Lamy: W-Will we be okay?
間に合わなくってアタフタするんじゃない?
Won't we just end up flustered because we didn't make it in time?
獅白ぼたん: まあ、それもあたしたちらしさってことで〜
Shishiro Botan: Well, that's just our style.
尾丸ポルカ: ノリでなんとかなるなる!
Omaru Polka: We'll manage with the flow!
雪花ラミィ: あ、そうだ、
Yukihana Lamy: Ah, right,
バンド名、どうするの?
What about the band name?
桃鈴ねね: えー、かっこいいやつがいいな〜!!
Momosuzu Nene: Hmm, I want something cool!
尾丸ポルカ: じゃあ、「青春★ピチピチフルスロットル団」!!
Omaru Polka: Then... "Youthful Peach-Peach Full Throttle Squad"!!
雪花ラミィ: だ……ダサい!?!?
Yukihana Lamy: That's... lame!?
獅白ぼたん: あ〜、もうちょい5期生要素も入れたいね。
Shishiro Botan: Hmm, I want to add more 5th Gen elements.
ラーメン、芝刈り機、低気圧……
Ramen, lawnmower, low pressure...
桃鈴ねね: 「カブトムシ」って入れたらかっこいいよ!!
Momosuzu Nene: It'd be cool if we put "Beetle" in it!
尾丸ポルカ: 「青春低気圧★ラーメンピチピチフルスロットル芝刈り機団」!!
Omaru Polka: "Youthful Low Pressure Ramen Peach-Peach Full Throttle Lawnmower Squad"!!
雪花ラミィ: 混ぜるな、ぐちゃぐちゃだよ!
Yukihana Lamy: Don't mix them together, it's a mess!
獅白ぼたん: じゃあ、ラミィちゃんは何がいいの?
Shishiro Botan: Then Lamy-chan, what do you suggest?
雪花ラミィ: え〜、やっぱりかわいいのがいいかな〜。
Yukihana Lamy: Well, I think something cute would be better...
「ねぽらぼハーモニー」とか♪
Like "NePoLaBo Harmony" or something.
尾丸ポルカ: それでいいのか、ラミィ
Omaru Polka: Are you sure about that, Lamy?
桃鈴ねね: かっこよくないよ、ラミィ
Momosuzu Nene: It's not cool, Lamy.
獅白ぼたん: 俺、恥ずかしいよ、ラミィ
Shishiro Botan: I'm embarrassed, Lamy.
雪花ラミィ: ほんっとに……お前らっ!!
Yukihana Lamy: Honestly... you guys!!
尾丸ポルカ: よ〜っし! バンド名も決まったし、やってみますか〜!!
Omaru Polka: Alright! Now that the band name is decided, shall we give it a go?
獅白ぼたん: これで、学寮祭の注目はいただきだ〜!!
Shishiro Botan: With this, we'll be the stars of the school festival!
雪花ラミィ: えっ、あれで行くの!?
Yukihana Lamy: Wait, we're going with THAT!?
桃鈴ねね: いくぞー! よーい……
Momosuzu Nene: Here we go! Ready...
全員: どん!!
Everyone: Boom!!
走って 走って
Run, run
憧れを越えて
Surpassing my yearnings
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
まだ見たことのない
Towards the other side
スピードの向こう側へ
Of speed I've never seen before
ウォームアップは完璧さ
Warm-up is perfect
地球をほら踏み込む鉄蹄
Look, iron hooves stepping onto the Earth
ゴール前のキセキ
The miracle before the goal
仕掛ける場所は最終コーナー
The final corner is where I'll make my move
あとは行けるとこまで息を切らしてたい
After that, I want to keep going till I'm out of breath
何万と手を叩くオーディエンス
Tens of thousands in the audience clapping their hands
割れんばかり響く大歓声
The deafening cheers echoing around
ファンファーレが鳴る
The fanfare sounds
心音が高まる
My heartbeat quickens
動き出す秒針
The second hand starts moving
夢のゲートが開く
The gate of dreams opens
いくぞー!
Here we go!
走って! 走って!
Run! Run!
憧れを追い越して
Surpassing my yearnings
次は誰の番だ?
Whose turn is it next?
さぁ目指せスーパースター
Now, aim to be a superstar
さあ！
Come on!
生きてく
I'll live on,
意味なんて
and the meaning behind it...
ぶっちギターの後で ついてくる
will follow after the guitar solo.
勝ちたい！ そう これは本能
I want to win! Yes, it's instinct.
走りたい！ 止まない衝動
I want to run! An unstoppable impulse.
叫びたい！ 勝利の雄叫びを
I want to shout! A victory cry!
轟け！
Let it roar!
誰かとバチバチ競うことでしか到達し得ない 輝かしいゴールライン
A glorious finish line that can only be reached by clashing with others.
Ah どんな理屈でも言語化できない感情
Ah, an emotion that no logic can put into words.
科学を超えて 葛藤超えて 熱い勝負したい したい したい
Beyond science, beyond conflict, I want to have a heated match.
どちらが最強か 決めようか好敵手
Let's decide who's the strongest, my worthy rival.
速い者が勝つ 何も言い訳はなしだ
The fastest wins, no excuses.
よーいどん！
Ready, set, go!
飛ばして
Fly high,
fly high,
涙さえ振り切って
shake off even the tears.
前に足を出したんだ 悩む暇なんてない
I took a step forward, there's no time to worry.
答えを！
The answer!
出すのは ゴールした後でも遅くない
It’s not too late to find it even after crossing the goal.
Go Fight!! 抗えぬ本能
Go Fight!! Irresistible instinct.
轟け！ 譲れない頂上
Roar! The summit I won't give up.
叫びたい！ 王者の雄叫びに
I want to shout! To the roar of the champion,
続け！
follow it!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
どんなことが起こったって
No matter what happens,
レースが止まらないように
so that the race doesn't stop,
ずっと続いていく この友情
this friendship will continue forever.
憎まれ口を叩いたって
Even if we trade insults,
みんな一列になれば
if we all line up together,
Ah てっぺんめがけて
Ah, aiming for the top,
位置について よーい
take your positions, ready...
走って
Run,
run,
走って
憧れを追い越して
surpassing our aspirations.
次は誰の番だ
Whose turn is it next?
さあ目指すはスーパースター
Come on, aim to be a superstar.
生きてく
I'll live on,
意味なんて
and the meaning behind it...
ぶっちギターの後で ついてくる
will follow after the guitar solo.
勝ちたい！ そう これは本能
I want to win! Yes, it's instinct.
走りたい！ 止まない衝動
I want to run! An unstoppable impulse.
叫びたい！ 勝利の雄叫びを
I want to shout! A victory cry!
轟け！
Let it roar!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
Ready!!
Steady!!
Derby!!
ひゃああ〜〜〜っ！ 冷たーいっ！
Waaaah! It's so cold!
バンドして汗かいちゃったからね〜 リフレッシュ、リフレッシュ♪
We got all sweaty from the band performance, so... Refresh, refresh!
ほら、おまるも早く進んで〜！
Come on, Omaru, move it!
あぁおあおあぁ〜〜〜〜〜〜 地獄シャワー無理〜〜〜！！！
Aaaargh! This hellish shower is impossible!!!
シャワー浴びて、プールで泳いで遊んだら… きっといいアイディアも出てくるってば！
If we take a shower and swim in the pool, I'm sure some good ideas will come to us!
…そう言って、毎回遊び疲れて終わるんだけどね〜〜
...You say that, but every time we just end up exhausted from playing.
でもさ！夏といえばプールでしょ！ ここで何かするのもアリじゃない？
But still! Summer means the pool! Wouldn't it be cool to do something here?
プールでできることといえば…… 撮影会！！
Speaking of things you can do at the pool... A photo shoot!!
ねねたちの水着姿で！
With us in our swimsuits!
お客さんを……悩・殺？
To... dazzle the fans?
ダメに決まってるだろ！ 会長に怒られるよ！！
Of course not! The President would be furious!!
絶対に盛り上がるのになぁ〜〜
But it would definitely be a hit...
……プールにラミちゃん沈めて 産地直送ラミィ水…これは売れる！！
...If we submerge Lamy-chan in the pool, we can sell fresh 'Lamy-water'... That would sell like crazy!!
そこっ！ラミィから出汁をとろうとするな！ ラミィ水は忘れろ！！
Hey! Stop trying to make broth out of Lamy! Forget about 'Lamy-water'!!
…じゃあ、ライブしとく？ プールサイドで！
...Well then, how about a live performance? By the poolside!
まぁ〜そうなるよねぇ〜！ でも夏、プール、歌…最高にマッチしてるっ！
Well, I guess that's what it comes down to! But summer, the pool, and singing... it's a perfect match!
いいねいいね！あの夏フェスの曲やろうよ〜！ 水鉄砲とか持って、みんなでびしょびしょになりながら！
Nice, nice! Let's do that summer festival song! We can bring water guns and all get soaking wet together!
え？でもあれってエモい感じの 恋愛ソングじゃなかった……？
Eh? But wasn't that an emotional love song...?
それをわたしたちなりに歌い上げるってことよ！
That's why we're going to sing it in our own way!
フェスにぴったりの選曲だからね！
It's the perfect song choice for a festival!
それじゃあ…終わらない夏にするぞーーー！！！
Alright then... Let's make this an endless summer!!!
おーーー！！！！
Yeah!!!
まだ照れくさいあいつとフェスに
I made a promise to go to a festival
行く約束をしたわ
with that guy I'm still embarrassed with
行く約束をしたわいいけど
Going is all well and good, but
あまり乗ってたら引かれそう
if I get too excited I might turn him off
控えめに楽しむって決めたんだ
I decided to enjoy it with some reserve
でも私の大好きな
But my favorite...
ロックスター 真夏のステージで
rock star on a stage in the middle of summer
スーツを着たロックスター もう
That rock star wearing a suit, I...
我慢できない！
I can't take it anymore!
止まらないのは私の汗
My sweat won't stop,
それとも君への気持ち？
or is it my feelings for you?
滴り落ちてく恋心
My love that flows and falls down
こぼれないようにすくってね
Scoop it up so it doesn't spill
止まらないのは夏への期待
My expectations for summer won't stop
忘れられない、
I can't forget,
夏になるかも
it might be a summer to remember
夏の日差しで焼け焦げそう
Summer sunlight makes me feel like I'm burning
すべてがスローモーションになる
Everything is in slow motion
他人の汗もどうでもよくて
I don't care about others' sweat
日差しのうだるさも感じない
I don't even feel the sweltering heat
でも私の大好きなロックスター
But my favorite rock star...
ラストの曲終わり
This is the last song,
ロックスター帰ってく
the rock star is going home
ライブが終わって我に帰って
The live is over, going back to my usual self
それから… それから…
And then... and then...
ずいぶん前のほうに来ちゃってたみたい
Looks like I came a bit too far ahead
さっきまで二人がいた場所、もう違う景色
The place where the two of us were, now a different scene
ああ、私やっちゃった
Oh, I did it
本気だったのに
Even though I was serious
うつむく私の隣に君が
With you next to me looking down
わたしの目を見つめる君
Looking into my eyes,
時間が止まってるみたい
you look like time has stopped
少し笑って君は言う
You say with a small smile
新しい君が見れたから
"I got to see a new side of you,
今日は本当に来て良かった
so I'm really glad I came today."
照れ笑いの奥見えちゃいそうで
You might end up seeing my embarrassed grin
私焦って目をそらした
So I quickly looked away
止まらないのは二人の恋だ
Our love won't stop
今年の夏よ
Summer of this year,
終わらないでよ。
please don't end.
はぁ〜〜……遊んだ遊んだっ♪
Phew! We sure had a lot of fun!
もう、くったくた… で、結局なん〜も決まってないっていう（笑）
I'm exhausted... and in the end, we didn't decide on anything at all! (laughs)
制服、洗濯に出しちゃったし… 今日の衣装、いつもの着替えしかないよ〜
I sent my uniform to the laundry... I only have my usual clothes for today's outfit.
もうこのままの格好で何かやるしかねーっ！
Well, we'll just have to do something in these clothes!
でもさ、やっぱりわたしたちにできることって… 歌とダンス、かな〜って思うんだよね〜
But you know, I think what we do best... is singing and dancing, after all.
うん。変に気取らずに、いつものわたしたちを見せるのが一番かも
Yeah. Maybe showing them our usual selves without any pretense is best.
よしっ！じゃあ歌う曲決めようよ！！
Alright! Then let's decide on the songs!
ねねは……エモい感じがいいな！いつもと違う感じの！
As for me... I want something emotional! Something different from usual!
ポルカは〜〜恋愛ソングやってみたいなぁっ
I'd really like to try singing a love song~
ラミィは元気いっぱい！合いの手たっぷりの盛り上がるやつ！！
Lamy wants something energetic! A real crowd-pleaser with lots of call-and-response!!
歌詞がグッと心にくる系の曲もいいなぁ〜
A song with lyrics that really touch your heart would be nice too.
あー...
Ah...
まぁ、あんなに運がバラバラだしね～
Well, everyone's luck was so scattered.
でも全部は無理くない？
But isn't doing it all impossible?
いや、できる！やってみなきゃ始まらない！
No, we can! It won't start if we don't try!
まさか...全部やる気？
No way... you're planning to do everything?
もちろん！どれか一つなんてもったいないでしょ！
Of course! Picking just one would be such a waste!
全部やって良いのがあるか考えよう！
Let's do them all and see what works!
ちょっとは休憩入れさせてね...
At least let us take a little break...
だったらさ！各自自分の部屋でやりたい曲をやっていこう！
In that case, let's each perform the songs we want in our own rooms!
じゃあまずはねねねからね！
Okay, starting with Nenene!
この曲は...ねねは違う服でやる！
For this song... Nene will change into different clothes!
わかった、やろうか～
Alright, let's do it.
今度こそ...これで出し物を決めるぞ～！
This time for sure... this will decide our performance!
じゃあ、やりますか！ねね、着替え終わった？
Alright, shall we start? Nene, finished changing?
オッケー！それじゃ、行きまーす！！
Okay! Well then, here I go!!
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if I’ve already forgotten
夏の木陰に座ったまま
Sitting in the shade of a summer tree
氷菓を口に放り込んで
Throwing an ice candy into my mouth
風を待っていた
Waiting for the wind to blow
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if I’ve already forgotten
世の中の全部嘘だらけ
The whole world is just a pack of lies
本当の価値を二人で
That we’d go find the true value
探しに行こうと笑ったこと
Together, and laughed
忘れないように
So I don’t forget
色褪せないように
So it doesn’t fade
形に残るものが
So it isn’t just about things
全てじゃないように
That leave a shape
言葉をもっと教えて
Teach me more words
夏が来るって教えて
Tell me that summer is coming
僕は描いている
I am drawing it
眼に映ったのは夏の亡霊だ
A ghost of summer reflected in my eyes
風にスカートが揺れて
A skirt sways in the wind
想い出なんて忘れて
Forgetting all about memories
浅い呼吸をする
Taking shallow breaths
汗を拭って夏めく
Wiping away sweat, it feels like summer
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if I’ve already forgotten
夏の木陰に座った頃
Back when I sat in the shade of a summer tree
遠くの丘から顔出した雲があったじゃないか
There was a cloud poking out from the hill, wasn't there?
君はそれを掴もうとして
You tried to grab it
馬鹿みたいに空を切った手で
With your hand cutting through the air like a fool
僕は紙に雲一つを書いて
I drew a single cloud on a piece of paper
笑って握って見せて
And laughed, grabbing it to show you
忘れないように
So I don’t forget
色褪せないように
So it doesn’t fade
歴史に残るものが
Because it isn’t about things
全てじゃないから
That remain in history
今だけ顔も失くして
For now, even losing my face
言葉も全部忘れて
Forgetting even all the words
君は笑ってる
You are laughing
夏を待っている僕ら亡霊だ
We are ghosts waiting for summer
心をもっと教えて
Teach me more of your heart
夏の匂いを教えて
Teach me the scent of summer
浅い呼吸をする
Taking shallow breaths
忘れないように
So I don’t forget
色褪せないように
So it doesn’t fade
心に響くものが
Because it isn’t about things
全てじゃないから
That resonate in the heart
言葉をもっと教えて
Teach me more words
さよならだって教えて
Teach me even about goodbye
今も見るんだよ
I’m still seeing it now
夏に咲いている花に亡霊を
A ghost in the flower that blooms in summer
言葉じゃなくて時間を
It’s not about words, it’s about time
時間じゃなくて心を
It’s not about time, it’s about the heart
浅い呼吸をする
Taking shallow breaths
汗を拭って夏めく
Wiping away sweat, it feels like summer
夏の匂いがする
It smells like summer
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if I’ve already forgotten
夏の木陰に座ったまま
Sitting in the shade of a summer tree
氷菓を口に放り込んで 風を待っていた
Popping an ice pop into my mouth, I was waiting for the wind.
土曜日は あえることが
On Saturdays, seeing each other...
当たり前に なって
...became something I took for granted,
不安からの あの気持ちが
And that feeling born from anxiety...
きえてちょっと寂しいの
...disappeared, making me a little sad.
一生分の キスの回数
A lifetime's worth of kisses...
すぐに超えちゃうよ
...we'll soon exceed them all.
まだ少し まだもっと
Just a bit more, no, even more...
特別でいたい ずっと
...I want to stay special, forever.
出会ってから付き合うまでの
From the moment we met until we started dating,
あの感じでいよう
let's keep that feeling alive.
わかってる ふりなんて
A facade of understanding...
100年後も いらない
...I won't need it even 100 years from now.
二人の合図が 増えたって
Even if our secret signals increase,
大事なこと言おう
let's keep saying the important things.
夏の日のはじまりを
The beginning of that summer day,
季節が変わっても 覚えてて
please remember it even as the seasons change.
Oh oh
月曜日は 会えないなら
If we can't meet on Monday,
次の日はどう？って
I'll ask "How about the next day?"
繰り返しの 言葉だって
Even if they are repetitive words,
それをもっと 言ってよね
please say them more often.
一回だけの キスのために
Just for a single kiss,
すぐに会いに行った
I went to see you right away.
あの時の あの場所は
That time and that place...
特別じゃないし ずっと
...aren't even special, and yet, forever...
出会ってから付き合うまでの
From the moment we met until we started dating,
あの感じでいよう
let's keep that feeling alive.
素っ気ない ふりなんて
Pretending to be indifferent...
かっこよくも ないよ
...isn't cool at all.
間違い ないこと 増えたって
Even if the things we're sure of increase,
幸せ ちょっと 違う
happiness feels a little different.
夏の日のはじまりが 正しい 恋よ
The beginning of that summer day is true love,
ほら 映してる
look, it's reflecting right now.
出会ってから付き合うまでの
From the moment we met until we started dating,
あの感じでいよう
let's keep that feeling alive.
わかってる ふりなんて
A facade of understanding...
100年後も いらない
...I won't need it even 100 years from now.
二人の合図が 増えたって
Even if our secret signals increase,
大事なこと言おう
let's keep saying the important things.
夏の日のはじまりを
The beginning of that summer day,
季節が変わっても 覚えてて
please remember it even as the seasons change.
Oh oh
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
High! High! High! High!
ねえ 歌うわ
Hey, I'll sing...
そうよ あなたに
Yes, for you.
甘えたいけれど 恥ずかしいかもね
I want to act spoiled, but maybe I'm embarrassed.
かもね Oi!
Maybe... Oi!
願い事の呪文 ほら
The spell of my wishes, look,
ムニャムニャムニャ～
Munya munya munya~
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
High! High! High! High!
ずっとこのまま時が 止まらぬかもね
Maybe this moment, this time, will never stop.
かもね
Maybe...
止まらぬかもね
It might not stop, maybe
かもね！オイ！
Maybe! Oi!
こういうのが恋なの
Is this what love is?
ドキドキドキーン
Thump, thump, thump!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
しかもね
Moreover...
かもね！オイ！
Maybe! Oi!
スキスキスキ
Love, love, love
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
昨日よりも
Even more than yesterday...
…かもね
...maybe
かもね！オイ！
Maybe! Oi!
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
…かもね
...maybe
かもね！オイ！
Maybe! Oi!
ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ ハイ
Hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
ねえ歌って
Hey, sing along
そうよあなたも
Yes, you too
乙女の気持ちが
I hope a maiden's feelings...
伝わるといいな
...will reach you
いいな！オイ！
How nice! Oi!
喉から出そうなくらい
So much it's about to burst out...
ラブララブ〜
...love-love-love!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
ずっとこのままあなた
Always staying this way...
素敵がいいな
...you're wonderful
いいな！オイ！
How nice! Oi!
こういうのははじめて
This is a first for me
ドキドキドキーン
Thump, thump, thump!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
ああいいな
Ah, how nice
いいな！オイ！
How nice! Oi!
スキスキスキ
Love, love, love
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
さっきよりも
Even more than before...
…いいな
...how nice
いいな！オイ！
How nice! Oi!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
いつだって新しいことに
Always, by new things...
君は心奪われてるから
...your heart is being stolen
クルクルと変わる
Ever-changing...
お天気 謎だらけ
...weather, full of mysteries
いつだってTVをつけても
No matter when I turn on the TV...
知りたいことは１つもないよ
...there's nothing I want to know
似たようなウワサ
Similar rumors...
ばかり 謎解きじゃない
...nothing but riddles
手に入れたいんだ 君の心の地図
I want to get my hands on the map of your heart
Ah 探し当てたい 宝物の在処
Ah, I want to find the location of the treasure
その心の奥を掴んで 揺さぶるものは何？
What is it that grabs your heart and shakes it?
考えているだけで 日が暮れる
Just thinking about it, the sun goes down
苦しくて 切なくて 楽しくて 日が暮れる
Painful, sad, enjoyable, the sun goes down
転がって ありえない 想像
Rolling around in impossible imagination
へこんだかと 思えば 笑ったり
Just when I think you're down, you're laughing
あたしは あたしで 相当 謎だらけ
I am, for my part, quite full of mysteries
ハマってしまったら 恋は迷路
Once you're hooked, love is a maze
Ah 角を曲がれば 行き止まりばかり
Ah, every corner I turn is just another dead end
物語の鍵を 握って遊んでいるのは誰？
Who is holding the key to the story and playing?
ずいぶん悪趣味なヒマ潰し
Such a vulgar pastime
退屈を弄ぶ 神様のヒマ潰し
Playing with boredom, God's pastime
ヒマ潰し
Killing time
このところの
These days...
...these days
不安な夜は
On anxious nights...
...on anxious nights
胸の奥の奥
Deep, deep in my chest...
...deep, deep in my chest
チリチリと鳴り響く
A tingly ringing echoes
Ah
会えない理由はわかってるのに
Even though I know the reason we can't meet
物語の鍵を握って
Who is the one playing...
遊んでいるのは誰？
...while holding the key to the story?
ずいぶん悪趣味なヒマ潰し
What a rather bad-taste way to kill time
その心の奥を掴んで
What is it that grabs your heart...
揺さぶるものは何？
...deep inside and shakes it?
考えてるだけで日が暮れて
Just thinking about it, the day comes to an end
苦しくて
It's painful,
切なくて
it's heartrending,
楽しくて
it's fun,
日が暮れて
and the day ends
苦しくて
It's painful,
切なくて
it's heartrending,
この恋に明け暮れる
I spend all my time in this love
つっ……疲れた〜〜！！
Phew... I'm tired~~!!
さすがに……ちょっと全員分連続は応えたね……
Doing everyone's parts in a row really took a toll...
でもでもっ！どの曲もサイコーだった〜〜♪
But but! Every song was the best~~♪
うん……。でも、“わたしたちらしさ”があるかって言われると、ちょっと悩むな〜
Yeah... but I wonder if it really had 'our style'~
（うーん……）
(Hmm...)
まもなく、学寮祭が始まります
The dormitory festival will begin shortly.
関係する生徒の皆さんは、速やかに準備をお願いします
Students involved, please prepare promptly.
やっ、やばい！！もう始まっちゃうってば〜〜っ！
Wait, oh no!! It's about to start already!
え〜〜お腹空いた〜〜 ちょっと購買行ってくるわっ！！
Eh~~ I'm hungry~~ I'm going to the store for a bit!!
じゃ、わたしも行く〜♪
Then I'll go too~♪
ラミィも行く〜〜！
Lamy's going too~~!
えぇ〜〜っ！？ちょっと〜〜！？
Eeeeh~~!? Wait a second~~!?
パン残ってるかな〜〜
I wonder if there's any bread left...
……ん？あれって……なんだ？？
...Hm? What's that...?
こ、これは……
T-This is...
もしかして……！
Could it be...!
もしかしくなくても！
Even if it isn't!
間違いな〜〜い！！
No mistake about it!!
NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade!
ねぽらぼ5周年グッズがこんなところに！！
NePoLaBo 5th Anniversary Goods are right here!!
きっと今日の配信終わりに出るやつだ！
This must be what's coming out after today's stream!
気になる！
I'm curious!
これは順番に見ていくしかないでしょ！
We have to look through these one by one!
まずは、プレミアムアクリル色紙！
First up, the Premium Acrylic Art Board!
今回のグッズのテーマが「花鳥風月」
The theme for these goods is 'Kacho Fugetsu'.
七原しえさんが描いてくれました！
Shie Nanahara drew this for us!
ねねたちの和服姿、綺麗でしょ〜
Nene and the others in kimonos, beautiful, right?
アクリル色紙にはねねたちの複製サインとロゴが入ってます
The board has our replicated signatures and logo.
アクリルの脚もついてるから、机に飾っておくこともできるよ
It has acrylic legs, so you can display it on a desk.
めっちゃ可愛いのでぜひ！
It's super cute, so please check it out!
次！
Next!
続いては、オフィシャルホロカスリーブ Anniversary Parade ねぽらぼVer.
Next is the Official Holoca Sleeves: NePoLaBo Ver.
もちろん、ホロカが入るスリーブです！
Of course, these are sleeves for Hololive cards!
1パック60枚入ってるから、
One pack has 60, so use them...
これでねぽらぼデッキを作り上げてください！
...to build your NePoLaBo deck!
いや、もう最近はね、ねぽらぼ全員出ちゃいましたから
Well, all of NePoLaBo have been released recently.
もうこれでね、お前のオリジナルの
So with this, build your original...
デッキ構築をして、優勝していくんだ！
...deck and go for the win!
さあ、お前ならできる、やるしかない！
Come on, you can do it, you have to!
見ているお前ら、ねぽらぼリスナー、お前ら頑張ってくれ！
All you NePoLaBo listeners, do your best!
次！
Next!
続いては、アクリルスタンド！
Next up, the Acrylic Stands!
プレミアムアクリル色紙とは別の表情をした、
These have different expressions from...
ラミィたちのアクリルスタンドです
...the Art Board. Acrylic Stands for Lamy and the rest!
「花鳥風月」で「花・春」が桃鈴ねね
In 'Kacho Fugetsu', 'Flower/Spring' is Momosuzu Nene.
「鳥・秋」が獅白ぼたん
'Bird/Autumn' is Shishiro Botan.
「風・夏」が尾丸ポルカ
'Wind/Summer' is Omaru Polka.
「月・冬」が雪花ラミィとなっています
And 'Moon/Winter' is Yukihana Lamy.
では、次！
Now, next!
最後は記念メダル！専用のケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルです
Last is the Commemorative Medal! It has a case and pouch.
それぞれタレントカラーと名前が入っていて、期生ごとにデザインが違うので
Each has their color and name, with unique designs.
コレクションアイテムとしてぜひ揃えてみてください
Please try to collect them all!
以上、NePoLaBo Anniversary Paradeのグッズでした！
That's all for the NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade goods!
それでは── これより、学寮祭を開始いたします。
Well then... From now, we will begin the festival.
ご来場の皆様、どうぞ最後までお楽しみください。
Everyone visiting, please enjoy until the end.
お、やばい！学寮祭始まってるって！
Oh, gosh! The festival is starting!
ねねたちも行かなきゃ！
We have to go too!
結局、何も買えなかったんだけど！
In the end, we couldn't buy anything!
しゃーなし。戻って学寮祭の話をしますか。
Can't be helped. Shall we head back and talk about the festival?
あで... えーっと... これは何をしているの？
Wait... uh... what are you doing?
ねねたちには、歌とダンスしかない！
For us, there's only singing and dancing!
ならばギリギリまで、全力で練習するしかないっしょー！！
Then we have to practice with all our might until the very last second!!
でも、もうお客さん入っているけどね。
But the audience is already inside.
あああ、もうやるしかないっ！
Ahhh, we just have to do it!
でもさ、肝心の何やるかを決めてないのでは？
But hasn't the most important thing—what we're going to do—not been decided yet?
でもさ、お客さんたちが見たいのって、やっぱり私たちらしさだよね。
But you know, what the audience wants to see is "us-ness" after all.
それなら... オリ曲じゃない？
If so... wouldn't it be our original songs?
じゃあ全部やろう！！
Then let's do them all!!
またーーー！？
Again!?
1つだけじゃダメダメ！ 衣装もぜーんぶ着替えて、たくさん歌おうよ！！
Just one isn't enough! Let's change into all our outfits and sing a lot!!
メドレーってこと？ お、いいじゃんそれ！
You mean a medley? Oh, that sounds good!
おおー、いいかも。
Ooh, that might be good.
で、順番はどうするの？
So, what about the order?
そんなんパッションでどうにかなるなる！！
That'll work out somehow with passion!!
こりゃ大変なことになりそうですね。
This looks like it's going to be a lot of work.
ししろん？どうしたの？
Shishiron? What's wrong?
いや、何か忘れている気がするんだけど... 思い出せない...
No, I feel like I'm forgetting something... but I can't remember...
大丈夫大丈夫！
It's okay, it's okay!
これを歌えば学寮祭は、ねねたちのもの！！
If we sing this, the festival will be ours!!
よっしゃいくぞー！！
Alright, let's go!!
私たちらしさ、見せるよ！
We'll show them our "us-ness"!
うんっ、とりあえずやるだけやろう！
Yeah, let's just do what we can!
せーのっ！ねぽらぼメドレー！！
One, two! Neopolabo Medley!!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, all the way across the sea
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so that it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
Our future shining with light
始めようか さあ Diving
Shall we begin? Now, diving
待っても意味ない Timing
No point in waiting, timing
でもたまに止まって Thinking Thinking
But sometimes stop and keep thinking, thinking
変えてみせる Change
I'll show you I can change
踏み出すのさ Stepping
Stepping forward
掴んでみせるよ キラキラ My Dream
I'll seize my sparkling dream
叶う日まで Story 繋ぐから
Until the day it comes true, I'll connect the story
だって君に ずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to keep watching me
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, all the way across the sea
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so that it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に Everybody
Come on, everybody together
Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Clap your hands, all the way across the sky
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, may it resonate
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
Our future shining with light
Hyper Jumpin' Now
Hyper Jumpin'
子どもくらい はしゃぐ方がお得でしょ
It's better to frolic like a child, right?
低気圧から 追い上がっていくテンション
Tension rising up from low pressure
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating speed just like this
辿り着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the destination
止まらない気持ちは 助走つけて
Gaining momentum with feelings that won't stop
次元を超えて行こう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Come on, Hyper Jumpin', let's leap
ハイになって 灰になるまで
Getting high until we turn to ash
Dancing Shake it up
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', all the way across the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Woh... Woh...
ドキドキしたい Give me give me give me love
I want my heart to throb, give me give me give me love
Woh... Woh...
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher
Don't say No No
好きなら More More More
If you like it, more, more, more
邪魔するノイズは 吹き飛ばせ Bang Bang Bang
Blow away the interfering noise, bang bang bang
遊びたいだけ アンチは無視して
Just want to play, ignore the haters
笑い飛ばして 蹴飛ばせ Kick it!
Laugh it off and kick it away, kick it!
Jump Around!!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
一歩目が 既に異空間
The first step is already a strange space
キラリ 渦に巻き込まれた？
Sparkling, did you get caught in the swirl?
違うよ 出会いたくって
No, I wanted to meet you
ホラみんなここにいる
Look, everyone is here
夢のようで… だけどね
It's like a dream... but you know
ファンタジーじゃない予感
A premonition that it's not a fantasy
流星群
Meteor shower
負けないよ
I won't lose
光放って！
Emit light!
どんな憧れも飛び越えて
Beyond any longing
銀河のまんなか行進しよう
Let's march in the middle of the galaxy
煌めきのシンフォニーさ
It's a symphony of sparkle
足跡だって星になる
Even footsteps become stars
1, 2, 3, Yeah! 奇跡散りばめ
1, 2, 3, Yeah! Sprinkled with miracles
1, 2, 3, Yeah! 何万光年を
1, 2, 3, Yeah! Tens of thousands of light years
1, 2, 3, Yeah! 眩しくてゆく季節が今
1, 2, 3, Yeah! The season that is dazzling right now
始まったんだよきっと
Must have just started
Wonderful Tour!
君に届け 星のメロディー
Deliver to you, the melody of the stars
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Stuffed tightly, tightly with our thoughts
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony played with you
これからも ずっと続いてく
It will continue forever
ねぇねぇ もっと近くにおいでよ
Hey, hey, come closer
回り始めた世界で踊らない？終わらない
Won't you dance in the world that has started to spin?
わくわく魔法かけたら
When you cast the excitement spell
ドキドキはSyncしてほらParty Time 止まらない
The pounding hearts sync up, look, it's Party Time
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
With our wishes
Twinkle Twinkle 夜空で歌いましょう
Twinkle Twinkle, let's sing in the night sky
君に響け 星のメロディー
Resound to you, the melody of the stars
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony played with you
これからも ずっと続いてく
It will continue forever
Twinkle 4 You
君に響け 星のメロディー
Resound to you, the melody of the stars
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation
君と繋がっている この宇宙(そら)に
In this sky where I'm connected to you
宝石を散りばめよう
Let's scatter some jewels
君に届け 星のメロディー
Deliver to you, the melody of the stars
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Stuffed tightly, tightly with our thoughts
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony played with you
これからも ずっと続いてく
It will continue forever
La La La La...
やっぱ ねぽらぼだなぁ〜!!
As expected of NePoLaBo!!
これで学寮祭は 大成功〜!!
With this, the Dormitory Festival is a huge success!!
あ〜……
Ah...
えっ、ししろん？ どうしたの？
Eh, Shishiron? What's wrong?
いやさ……確かに良かったんだけど……
Well... it was certainly good, but...
なんかこう……何かを忘れてる気がするんだよね
I feel like... we've forgotten something.
何言ってんの!?
What are you talking about!?
このメドレーで完璧だったってば！
This medley was perfect!
そうだよ〜！
That's right!
これでみ〜んな、ひとつになってハッピー!!
With this, everyone's become one and happy!!
来てくれた人たちも、きっと
I'm sure the people who came
ラミィたちの声を聴いて、喜んでくれたよ！
heard our voices and were happy!
ひとつ……声……
One... voice...
あッ!!!
Ah!!!
私たち、新曲作ってたじゃん!!
We were making a new song, weren't we!!
あッ……
Ah...
わすれてたあーーーー!!!
I forgot it!!!
ねねたち、あんなに練習したのに〜ッ!!
We practiced so much!!
ねねたち、あんなに練習したのに～っ！
We practiced so hard...!
作ったのはいいけど......「出すタイミングどうしよう」って言ってたら、
It was good that we made it, but while we were wondering when to use it...
完全に忘れてた......
...we completely forgot about it.
出すタイミング絶対にここだったな～
This was definitely the time to use it.
もうステージ真っ暗だし～～～！
The stage is already pitch black!
......お客さん......まだ、いてくれてる、かな......
...I wonder if... the audience is still there...
......大丈夫！ 今なら、まだ......ギリギリ間に合うっ！！
...It's okay! We can still... just barely make it!!
ねえ！ そこの君！！ まだ......見てくれているよね？
Hey! You there!! You're still... watching, right?
ねねたちの、新しい曲──聴いてくれる？
Will you listen to... our new song?
うん、うん......きっと、聴いてくれるって信じてる！
Yeah, yeah... I'm sure they'll listen to us!
最後まで一緒に盛り上がっていこうね！
Let's all have a blast together until the end!
それではあらためて......んんっ......聴いてください──ねぽらぼの新曲です
And now, once again... *ahem*... Please listen to... Nepolabo's new song.
この先、みんなとなら、どこまでも行けると願って──歌います
Hoping that we can go anywhere if we're together... we will sing.
5周年──その先の未来もずっと、一緒に見守り......歩んでください
5th anniversary... Please continue to watch over us and walk with us into the future.
1人じゃ辿り着けない場所へ......みんなで──
To a place we couldn't reach alone... all together--
ひとつになる声
Voices becoming one
暗闇の中で 見つけた声
A voice found in the darkness
そのしるべを 辿りながら
While following that signpost
僕らは 走るよ
We are running
ひとつになる声
Voices Becoming One
ひとりぼっちだった日
The days when I was all alone
先見えなかった日
The days when I couldn't see ahead
だけど君と出会えて
But then I met you
そっと扉を開けた
And softly opened the door
手のひらの中に また1を足して
Adding one more into the palm of my hand
何度も奇跡を叶えよう
Let's make miracles happen over and over again
澄み渡る空の彼方
Beyond the clear blue sky
太陽と踊る
Dancing with the sun
羽になる
I become wings
情熱が突き動かす
Passion drives us forward
僕らの明日を 照らして
Shining on our tomorrow
同じ夢を駆ける僕らは
We, who chase the same dream
強く心を結んで
Bound our hearts tightly together
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから
We can go anywhere, to the ends of the world
これからまた続いてく道
On the road that continues from here
1人じゃ辿り着けない
We couldn't reach it alone
だから この背中預けるよ
So I'll entrust my back to you
信じている
I believe in you
君の手を
In your hand
僕らの未来を
In our future
みんなの声を
In everyone's voices
君らしいって思う
I think it's just like you
その積み重ねが
That accumulation of moments
なぜか嬉しくなるの
Makes me happy for some reason
きっとこれからもそう
I'm sure it'll stay that way
手のひらの中の
Within the palm of my hand
大切な日々が
Those precious days
沢山の光を奏でて
Play countless lights
君と笑った
And I laughed with you
始まりの時の願い
The wish from when it all began
今もほら輝いてる
Look, it's still shining now
未来まで連れてゆこう
Let's take it with us to the future
暗闇を抜けた先に
Beyond the darkness
みんなの笑顔 見つけた
I found everyone's smiles
同じ夢を駆ける僕らは
We, who chase the same dream
強く心を結んで
Bound our hearts tightly together
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから
We can go anywhere, to the ends of the world
これからまた続いてく道
On the road that continues from here
1人じゃ辿り着けない
We couldn't reach it alone
だから この背中預けるよ
So I'll entrust my back to you
信じている
I believe in you
君の手を
In your hand
僕らの未来を
In our future
みんなの声を
In everyone's voices
ひとつに
As one
みんなの声を
Everyone's voices
重ねて
Layering together
みんなの声を
Everyone's voices
ひとつに
As one
みんなの声を
Everyone's voices
重ねて
Layering together
みんなの声を
Everyone's voices
ひとつに
As one
ひとつに 心合わせて
As one, with our hearts united
重ねて
Layering together
僕らは願う
This is our wish
ひとつに 光の中で
As one, within the light
重ねて
Layering together
ひとつになる声
Our voices becoming one
ねぽらぼ学園
☆5周年記念！！輝く学寮祭☆
NePoLaBo Academy
☆5th Anniversary!! Shining Dormitory Festival☆